kixify.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy | Kixify Marketplace

Effective October 16, 2013

To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used when you access Kixify’s website or mobile app (the “Website”). We are committed to protecting your privacy and committed to developing technology that gives you the most powerful and secure online experience.

This privacy statement covers personally identifiable information, anonymous data collection and aggregate reporting. Personally identifiable information is any information that is associated with your name or personal identity.

**What we collect**

During the registration process, the types of personal information you provide to us may include, name, address, phone, email address, username and password. If you are not a registered user and you purchase an item through Kixify, you will be required to provide shipping and email addresses, which will be shared with the Seller. The Seller’s shipping information will be contained in the receipt provided to the Buyer.

When you browse our web site, you do so anonymously. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our web site you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our web site. Like many other commercial web sites, the Website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the Website. Please go to "Use of Cookies" below for more information.

**How we use it**

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not making you enter your personal information more than once.
  * To permit Sellers to ship items to Buyers.
  * To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you of product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services provided from Kixify.
  * To provide feedback in an online survey.
  * To request assistance or fill out support requests.

**Who we share it with**

We never sell or rent your personal information. We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law (for example, a subpoena) or regulation, or in good faith to (a) comply with legal processes served on the site, or (b) protect the rights and property of Kixify, or (c) where our records indicate fraudulent activity or other deceptive practices that a governmental agency should be made aware of, or (d) where your communication suggests possible harm to others.

When you register, we will not share your information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above. We use personal information to reply to inquiries, handle complaints, provide operational notices, keep records up to date to notify you via periodic e-mails of technical service issues, specials, or other related product/service information. Your information may be shared with our agents or contractors for the purpose of performing service for Kixify.

**Paypal**

All Kixify transactions are processed by Paypal. Your use of Paypal’s services is governed by the Paypal Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Kixify strictly protects the security of your personal information. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. Inside the company, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access.

You also have a significant role in protecting your information. No one can see or edit your personal information without knowing your username and password, so do not share these with others.

We use SSL encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data.

**Access to your Personal Information**

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may review and update this information at any time by logging into your account.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity, such as password and username, before granting access to your data.

**Use of Cookies**

Our web sites are not setup to track, collect or distribute personal information. Our site does generate certain kinds of non-identifying site usage data, such as number of hits and visits to our sites. This information is used for internal purposes only. The statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

The Website uses "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Website or our services.

**Problems or complaints with Our Privacy Policy**

We value your comments and opinions. If you have questions, comments or a complaint about compliance with this privacy policy you may contact us.
